var questions =[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "Who designed the national flag of india?",
        answer : "Pingali Venkayya",
        options : [
            "Pingali Venkayya",
            "Gopal Krishan",
            "Gokhale Dadabhai",
            "Naroji Pherozeshah Mehta"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 2,
        question :"Who designed the national flag of pakistan?",
        answer : "Ameer-ud-din Qadwai",
        options : [
            "Abdur-rehman Chugtai",
            "Liaquat Ali",
            "Chaudhary Rehmat Ali",
            "Ameer-ud-din Qadwai"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 3,
        question :"What is the meaning of pakistan? ",
        answer : "Muslim Land",
        options : [
            "Muslim Land",
            "Land of five rivers",
            "Desert",
            "Holy Land"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 4,
        question :"Who is the first Governal General of pakistan? ",
        answer : "Muhammah Ali Jinnah",
        options : [
            "Muhammah Ali Jinnah",
            "Liaquat Ali Khan",
            "Ayub Khan",
            "Iskandar Mirza"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 5,
        question :"What was the major event of 1971?",
        answer : "Bangladesh broke away from pakistan",
        options : [
            "Bangladesh broke away from pakistan",
            "Explosion of nuclear bomb",
            "Tashkent Agreement",
            "Nawaz Sharif beacame prime minister"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 6,
        question :"When Musharraf overthrew the goverment of Nawaz Sharif What designation did the take?",
        answer : "Prime Minister",
        options : [
            "Dictator",
            "Consul",
            "Prime Minister",
            "Chief Executive"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 7,
        question :"In which year did pakistan win the cricket World Cup?",
        answer : "1975",
        options : [
            "1975",
            "1987",
            "1992",
            "1996"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 8,
        question :"When did pakistan win Olympic gold medal in Hockey for the first time?",
        answer : "1952",
        options : [
            "1948",
            "1952",
            "1960",
            "1964"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 9,
        question :"Which is the national flower of pakistan? ",
        answer : "Jasmine",
        options : [
            "Rose",
            "Thistle",
            "Jasmine",
            "camomille"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 10,
        question :"Which is the national language of pakistan? ",
        answer : "Urdu",
        options : [
            "Hindhi",
            "Bengali",
            "Tamil",
            "Urdu"
        ]
    },
];